Guide to the Planned Community Archives collection, 1960-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 9: Media 1960-2004
  - Subseries 2: Slides, 1960-1990
    - Lake Anne Village Center-the Lake, 1970s (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Architectural elevation for the Lake Anne Village Center, color", August 1964; 6.
    - Lake Anne Village Center-Models, 1970s (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Architectural elevation of the Lake Anne area, color", June 1966; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Architectural model of the Reston community center, in First Village Community Center, color", June 1964; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Architectural elevation for the art gallery in the First Village Community Center, black and white", no date; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Architectural elevation for a nursery school in the First Village Community Center, black and white", no date; 4.
    - Landscape, People and Houses, 1980s-1990s (Box 174, Folder 1)
      611
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside homes in Reston", ca. 1988; 1.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Some of Reston's lakeside homes as seen during an autumn sunset", 1988; 2.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Community festival and vintage automobile in a parade", 1988; 3.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Exterior view of a single-family home in Reston", 1988; 4.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Aerial view of Reston near the United States Geological Survey headquarters", 1987; 5.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Aerial view of Reston's community clusters and villages cast in an autumn sunset", 1987; 6.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Aerial view of Reston's community clusters and villages cast in an autumn sunset", 1987; 7.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Choosing a pumpkin from one of Reston's pumpkin patches", 1988; 8.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Single-family home in Reston in the middle of construction", 1988; 9.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Single-family home in Reston nearly completed", 1988; 10.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Reston town homes in the middle of construction under review by the architectural board", 1988; 11.
      - Slide: Vince Ahren, "Town homes in Reston", 1987; 12.
    - People, 1980s (Box 175, Folder 1)
      612
      - Slide: Ander, "Reston residents enjoy an evening at the greater Reston arts center", no date; 1.
      - Slide: Ander, "Young man examines an art label at the greater Reston arts center, tribal masks", no date; 2.
    - People, 1980s (Box 176, Folder 1)
      613
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston International Center covered in snow", no date; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Patrick Kane", August 1982; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston artist shows off her talent at community festival", ca. 1976; 3.
    - People, 1980s (Box 177, Folder 1)
      614
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "Reston family piles into a vintage automobile for an afternoon drive, image was used in a print ad", no date; 1.
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "Reston family piles into a vintage automobile for an afternoon drive, image was used in a print ad", no date; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Bowman Distillery", June 1966; 3.
    - Miscellaneous Buildings and Shopping Centers, 1970s (Box 178, Folder 1)
      615
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "Sperry sign in Reston's industrial park", no date; 1.
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "National Art Education Association sign in Reston", no date; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Music Educators National Conference sign in Reston", July 1982; 3.
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "Construction begins on another project in Reston", July 1982; 4.
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "Construction begins on another project in Reston", July 1982; 5.
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "American Press Institute sign outside offices in Reston", no date; 6.
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "GTE facility under construction in Reston's industrial park", ca. 1982; 7.
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "GTE facility under construction in Reston's industrial park", ca. 1982; 8.
      - Slide: Robert Llewellyn, "United States Geological Survey front exterior with American flag", May 1978; 9.
      - Slide: Robert Llewellyn, "United States Geological Survey front exterior with American flag", May 1978; 10.
      - Slide: Robert Llewellyn, "Exterior corner of the United State Geological Survey headquarters in Reston", May 1978; 11.
      - Slide: Don A. Sparks, "Aerial view of Reston International Center and golf courses", July 1981; 12.
      - Slide: Robert Llewellyn, "Aerial view of the Reston International Center and adjacent Sheraton hotel", July 1981; 13.
    - Reston, 1980s (Box 179, Folder 1)
      616
      - Slide: Anthony J. Sylvestro, "Aerial view of the Reston International Center and adjacent Sheraton hotel", January 1986; 1.
    - Boating, 1970s (Box 180, Folder 1)
      618
    - Reston, 1980s (Box 181, Folder 1)
      619
      - Slide: James Kirby, "Broadlands exterior sign flanked by landscaping", no date; 1.
    - Boating, 1970s (Box 182, Folder 1)
      621
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "Residents enjoying a sunny afternoon on Lake Anne", June 1982; 1.
      - Slide: Schnabel Photography, "Private sailboat on one of Reston's inlets", ca. 1982; 2.
    - Buses, 1970s (Box 183, Folder 1)
      622
    - Roads, 1970s (Box 183, Folder 2)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Roads near Reston under construction", May 1973; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Roads near Reston under construction, RIC to the left", May 1973; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Roads near Reston under construction with the Reston International Center off to the left", May 1973; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Dulles Highway under construction, will become the Dulles Toll Road, RIC off to the right", ca. 1983; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of local highways near Reston, just left of the RIC", July 1981; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Roads near Reston under construction", June 1989; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Roads near Reston under construction", no date; 7.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Early construction begins on Sunrise Valley Drive", September 1976; 8.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Brand new Sunrise Valley Drive", September 1976; 9.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lawyers Road in Reston", September 1976; 10.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Roads near Reston under construction", May 1969; 11.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Route 606 before becoming four lanes of traffic", November 1972; 12.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Roads near Reston under construction", no date; 13.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Wiehle Avenue and Sunset Hills Road", November 1972; 14.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Sunrise Valley Drive looking across from the United States Geological Survey", January 1974; 15.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Construction at Heather Knoll", March 1992; 16.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside homes construction in Reston", March 1992; 17.
    - Streetscape, 1980s (Box 183, Folder 3)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hunter Mill looking west at Sunrise Valley Drive", July 1980; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Sunrise Valley Drive looking south from Wiehle Avenue", July 1980; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Avenue at Glade looking northeast", July 1980; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Wiehle Avenue to Sunrise Valley Drive looking south", July 1980; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Reston Avenue streetscape", June 1966; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Streetscape looking at Lake Anne plaza and Heron House", March 1967; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Sunrise Valley Drive at Soapstone Drive looking northeast", July 1980; 7.
    - Miscellaneous Buildings, 1970s (Box 184, Folder 1)
      623
      - Slide: Don A. Sparks, "Aerial view of construction in Reston's industrial park", July 1981; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of construction in Reston's industrial park", June 1979; 2.
      - Slide: Don A. Sparks, "Aerial view of construction in Reston's industrial park", July 1981; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of a single-family housing cluster under construction in Reston", June 1979; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of construction projects in Reston", June 1979; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of housing cluster construction in Reston", June 1979; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of housing cluster construction in Reston", June 1979; 7.
      - Slide: Don A. Sparks, "Aerial view of housing cluster construction in Reston", July 1981; 8.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of lakeside town homes on Lake Anne", October 1980; 9.
      - Slide: Ahren, Kemp, and Associates, "Exterior view of completed building in Reston's industrial park", no date; 10.
      - Slide: Ahren, Kemp, and Associates, "Construction continues in Reston's industrial park", no date; 11.
    - Shopping Centers, 1980s (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Brown's Chapel", October 1979; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside town homes under construction", April 1965; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Looking at the swimming pool in nearby housing cluster from atop Heron House", July 1965; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Washington Plaza Village Center during construction phase", October 1965; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of architectural elevation of Reston's first village center, Lake Anne, black and white", ca. 1961; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Nighttime festivities at Washington Plaza Village center", no date; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Construction begins at one of the lakeside village centers in Reston", no date; 7.
    - Bowling, Bicycling, Basketball, Baseball, School Day Care and Signs, 1960s-1970s (Box 185, Folder 1)
      624
      - Slide: Susanne Anderson, "Construction continues at Terraset Elementary School", no date; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Early stages of construction at Langston Hughes/South Lakes Intermediate School", October 1979; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Architectural elevation for an elementary school in Reston, color", August 1966; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Architectural model for one of Reston's schools [does not specify between elementary, intermediate, or secondary]", May 1964; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Site plan for Reston elementary school, color", April 1964; 5.
      - Slide: Phil Quinn, "Solar panels are installed on the roof of Terraset Elementary School", no date; 6.
      - Slide: Phil Quinn, "Solar panels are installed on the roof of Terraset Elementary School", no date; 7.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Construction continues at Terraset Elementary School", no date; 8.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Construction continues at Terraset Elementary School", no date; 9.
      - Slide: Susanne Anderson, "Roof construction on Terraset Elementary School", no date; 10.
      - Slide: Susanne Anderson, "Roof construction on Terraset Elementary School", no date; 11.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "School bus in front of Terraset Elementary", no date; 12.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "View of nearly completed Terraset Elementary", no date; 13.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of Terraset Elementary under construction", no date; 14.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "School bus in front of Terraset Elementary", no date; 15.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Exterior view of Terraset Elementary School", no date; 16.
    - Transportation, 1970s (Box 186, Folder 1)
      625
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Road Improvements map of Reston and surrounding environs", no date; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Looking east along Glade approaching the intersection with Colts Neck Road", October 1973; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Hunter Mill looking west to Sunrise Valley Drive", July 1980; 3.
    - Walkways, 1970s (Box 186, Folder 2)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Residents strolling along one of the designated pedestrian walkways", July 1971; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Pedestrian walkway and underpass with a mural in progress", ca. 1971; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Lakeside town home cluster, Mallard's Landing", ca. 1980; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Resident treks across a pedestrian walkway on a snowy day in March", March 1969; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Construction on the pedestrian overpass", June 1970; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Construction on the pedestrian overpass", June 1970; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Pedestrian walkway near Reston Avenue under construction", July 1971; 7.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Pedestrian walkway near Reston Avenue under construction", July 1971; 8.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "View of the pedestrian bridge from the top of Heron House", May 1965; 9.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Pedestrian overpass construction completed and in full use", ca. 1970; 10.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Pedestrian bridge in use over Lake Anne", April 1973; 11.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Male resident with dog emerge from the pedestrian walkway near Reston Avenue with completed mural", ca. 1971; 12.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Architectural model for a pedestrian walkway", ca. 1969; 13.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Pedestrian walkways and bridges", January 1966; 14.
    - People, 1970s (Box 187, Folder 1)
      626
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Exterior view of lakeside home under construction, possibly Mallard's Landing", August 1980; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Surveyor takes measurements with specialized equipment", no date; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Planners and architects confer with blueprints", no date; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Planners and architects confer with blueprints", no date; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Construction continues on town homes", no date; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Construction continues on town homes", no date; 6.
    - Original Production Slides used in Produced Pieces and Advertisements, 1980s (Box 188, Folder 1)
      627
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Planners discussing the conceptual designs for the South Lakes Village Center", ca. 1975; 1.
      - Slide: Cameron Davidson, "Entrance to Tandem Computer Headquarters in Reston", September 1982; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Businessman on the telephone and using computer", no date; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of Lake Anne Plaza and Heron House, image used in the 1983 Fall newsletter", ca. 1983; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Conceptual design for the South Lakes Village Center", ca. 1981; 5.
      - Slide: Don A. Sparks, "House construction with designers discussing the plans", July 1981; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Man in front of South Lakes High School, possibly the principal", ca. 1982; 7.
    - Gymnastics, Recreational Frisbee, Football, Fishing, Boating/Sailing and Golfing, 1970s (Box 189, Folder 1)
      628
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Boys fishing from pier in one of Reston's village centers", August 1967; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Boy fishing from dock near Lake Anne while girl watches", ca. 1967; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Father and son fishing from pier in one of Reston's village centers", ca. 1967; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Children staring at water from dock in one of Reston's village centers", ca. 1967; 4.
    - Reston, 1980s (Box 190, Folder 1)
      629
    - Bowling, Bicycling, Basketball, Baseball, School Day Care and Signs, 1970s (Box 191, Folder 1)
      630
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Three friends pose in front of Hunters Woods Elementary school", ca. 1971; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Construction continues at Terraset Elementary school", ca. 1971; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Children playing in school yard at Lake Anne Elementary school", May 1971; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Terraset Elementary School sign", 1980; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Herndon High School sign", February 1993; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Aerial view of Dogwood Elementary School", October 1976; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "South Lakes High School under construction", September 1976; 7.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "South Lakes High School under construction but nearly completed", ca. 1977; 8.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Children running in front of Hunters Woods Elementary School", ca. 1971; 9.
    - D.C., Dulles Airport, New York City and Outside Reston Residential, 1970s (Box 192, Folder 1)
      631
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Tyson's Corner", ca. 1975; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Tyson's Corner", ca. 1961; 2.
    - Reston, 1970s (Box 193, Folder 1)
      632
    - Reston, 1970s (Box 194, Folder 1)
      633
      - Slide: Dean Hawthorne, "Westcove cedar town homes", September 1982; 1.
      - Slide: Dean Hawthorne, "Westcove cedar town homes", September 1982; 2.
      - Slide: Dean Hawthorne, "Westcove cedar lakeside town homes under construction", September 1982; 3.
    - Reston, 1970s (Box 195, Folder 1)
      634
      - Slide: Anthony Hathaway, "Recreational boating at Washington Plaza", no date; 1.
      - Slide: Anthony Hathaway, "Recreational boating at Washington Plaza", no date; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Recreational sailing on Lake Anne", no date; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Recreational boating on one of Reston's lakes", no date; 4.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Male resident retrieves oars for canoes", no date; 5.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Residents gather and prepare for what appears to be a canoe race", no date; 6.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Couple sail away after completing a shopping excursion at the Lake Anne Village Center", no date; 7.
      - Slide: Robert Llewellyn, "Golfer in the shadow of the Reston International Center", October 1978; 8.
    - Reston, 1980s (Box 196, Folder 1)
      635
    - Fellowship House, 1980s (Box 197, Folder 1)
      636
    - Fox Mills Apartments, 1980s (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Glenvale Condo, 1970s (Box 197, Folder 3)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Glenvale Condominiums completed models", June 1973; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Conceptual designs for the Glenvale Condominiums", July 1971; 2.
    - The Green Apartments, 1970s (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Harbor Point Condo, 1970s (Box 197, Folder 5)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Architectural rendering of the Harbor Point condominiums", June 1978; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Harbor Point condominiums completed models", ca. 1981; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Conceptual designs for the Harbor Point condominiums", November 1979; 3.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Conceptual designs for the Harbor Point condominiums", April 1981; 4.
    - Hernon House Condo, 1970s (Box 197, Folder 6)
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Heron House as seen from Lake Anne", ca. 1972; 1.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Heron House condominiums and Reston resident", April 1973; 2.
      - Slide: Anonymous, "Washington Plaza condominiums and Heron House", October 1972; 3.
    - Hunters Woods Apartments, 1970s (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Northgate Apartments, 1970s (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - D.C., Dulles Airport, New York City and Outside Reston Residential, 1970s (Box 198, Folder 1)
      637
  - Subseries 3: Audio-Cassettes and CD, 1984-2004
    The subseries is comprised of interviews with individuals involved in the development of Reston and the CD's are a variety of Reston related information.
    - Eckert, George-Interview (Cassette), 1984 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - El-Ezaby, Mohammed-Interview (Cassette), 1984 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Grady, Fran and Jim-Interview (Cassette), 1984 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Grady, Fran and Jim-Interview (Cassette), 1984 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Healy, Mike-Interview (Cassette), 1984 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Linberg, Carolyn-Interview (Cassette), 1985 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Reston Today (Cassette), 1980s (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Reston Town Center (Cassette), 1990 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Reston Town Center (Cassette), 1990s (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Saunders, Glenn W. (Jr.)-Interview (Cassette), 1984 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Scherzer, John-Interview (Cassette), 1984 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Zacko, Dr. George and Donna-Interview (Cassette), 1984 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - "Reston Today" and "Sixty Minutes of Sound Advice" (Cassette), 1980s (Box 200, Folder 1)
      14.2
    - Reston Related (CD), 2004 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Reston Related (CD), 2004 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Reston Related (CD), 2004 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Reston Related (CD), 2004 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Reston Related (CD), 2004 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Reston Related (CD), 2004 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - William and Mary Jane Scurlock (CD), 1989 (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 4: Negatives, 1987-1991
    This is a small subseries contained of negatives of various views from around Reston.
    - Reston Community, 1990s (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Reston Community, 1987-1991 (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 5: Video, 1970-1995
    The subseries contains programs about planned communities. The majority of the videos are interviews from WETA. The videotapes include interviews with Robert Simon, Martha Pennino and others. There are also taped events, such as the Reston Festival and different programs, for example "The Rise of New Towns". There are additional WETA videotapes in series 11.
    - Reston History (Lake Anne to Hickory)-Reel, 1972 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Reston History (Vernon Walker at Fairfax Water Treatment Plant)-Reel, 1971 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - List of WETA Tapes, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 1)
      26.1
    - Allen, Betty, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 2)
      26.2
    - Black Focus Festival, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 3)
      26.3
    - Bowman, Mr and Mrs, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 4)
      26.4
    - Brandenburg, J., 1986 (Box 202, Folder 5)
      26.5
    - Frye, Dolores, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 6)
      26.6
    - Head, Mona, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 7)
      26.7
    - Jennings, Sibley, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 8)
      26.8
    - Kennedy, Pat, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 9)
      26.9
    - Land, David, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 10)
      26.10
    - Nicoson, Bill, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 11)
      26.11
    - Pennino, Martha, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 12)
      26.12
    - Rucker, Embry and Priscilla Ames, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 13)
      27.1
    - Saunier, Gayle, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 14)
      27.2
    - Seidel, Martha Ruth, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 15)
      27.3
    - Siegal, Martin (Rabbi), 1986 (Box 202, Folder 16)
      27.4
    - Simon, Robert, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 17)
      27.5
    - Skolnick, Elaine, Harry Zubkov and Betty, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 18)
      27.6
    - Stowers, Joseph, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 19)
      27.7
    - Taylor, Ralph, 1986 (Box 203, Folder 1)
      27.8
    - Weaver, Fred, 1986 (Box 203, Folder 2)
      27.9
    - Weidonfield, Gil (Mayor of Greenbelt), 1986 (Box 203, Folder 3)
      27.10
    - Whitelsey, Julian, 1986 (Box 203, Folder 4)
      27.11
    - Von Eckhardt, Wolf, 1986 (Box 203, Folder 5)
      27.12
    - Allen, Betty, September 23, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 1)
      49.2
    - Allen, Betty, September 23, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 2)
      49.3
    - Allen, Betty, September 23, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 3)
      49.4
    - Allen, Betty-Greenbelt, September 23, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Brandenburg, John G.-Columbia, November 4, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 5)
      38.6
    - Brandenburg, John G.-Columbia, November 4, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 6)
      39.1
    - Brandenburg, John G.-Columbia, November 4, 1986 (Box 205, Folder 1)
      41.1
    - Brandenburg, John G.-Columbia, November 4, 1986 (Box 205, Folder 2)
      38.5
    - B-Roll, Columbia, November 17, 1986 (Box 205, Folder 3)
      40.1
    - B-Roll, Columbia, November 17, 1986 (Box 205, Folder 4)
      40.2
    - Bryne/Lee-Columbia B-roll, November 17, 1986 (Box 205, Folder 5)
      39.2
    - Byrne/Lee-Columbia B-roll, November 17, 1986 (Box 205, Folder 6)
      39.3
    - Byrne/Lee-Columbia B-roll, November 17, 1986 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Byrne/Lee-Columbia B-roll, November 17, 1986 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Columbia-Cutaways, November 2, 1986 (Box 206, Folder 3)
      41.5